https://morrisyachts.com/privacy-legal/

Privacy & LegalPrivacy Policy Last updated: March 3, 2020This Privacy Policy describes the practices of The
Hinckley Company (“we”, “us”, “our” or “Hinckley”) with respect to information
we collect from and about users (“you”, “your” or “users”) of our websites located
at http://www.hinckleyyachts.com, http://www.huntyachts.com, http://www.morrisyachts.com and http://www.hinckleysportboats.com (“Website”).This Privacy Policy applies only to information
collected by Hinckley via the Website and specifically does not apply to information
collected (1) by us through other channels, such as offline, or (2) by third
parties whose forms or other collection mechanisms may be embedded in or linked
to or accessible from the Website. By using the Website, you acknowledge that you have
read and understand the terms of this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy may be revised
periodically, and any such revisions will be reflected by the effective date
above.  Please revisit this page to stay
aware of any changes. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we
will provide you with additional notice of such changes by providing alerts
within the Website.Collection and Use of User Information.Through the Website, Hinckley may collect certain
types of information from and about you, and other information regarding your
usage of the Website. We may collect this information in several different
ways, including directly from you when you provide it to us, such as by filling
in forms on the Website, and through the use of automatic data collection
technologies, such as via server logs and Google Analytics (more information
below).We collect
the following types of information from or about users of our Website:Contact
Information: If you request information
about Hinckley’s yachts or services, we may collect information you provide to
us in connection with such activity, such as your name and email address and
any messages you send us (“Contact Information”), so that we can reply to or
otherwise fulfill your request.Usage
Data: We collect details regarding your usage of the
Website (“Usage Data”) to present, personalize, improve and maintain our
Website.Metrics: We collect anonymized metrics regarding usage of
the Website (“Metrics”) to present, improve and maintain our Website, and to
gather aggregate information about the Website’s user base.Automatic Data Collection TechnologiesWe collect Usage Data and Metrics using automatic data collection
technologies, as described below.When you interact with the Website, servers
automatically record usage information that your browser or device sends such
as IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages,
operating system, date/time stamps, and related data. This information may be
stored in log files, and helps us analyze how our users interact with and use
the Website, compile reports on the Website’s activity, and provide maintenance
and other services related to the Website’s activity and usage.The Website also uses the web analytics service
Google Analytics, which uses cookies and other tracking technologies. Cookies
are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit
certain websites. Cookies may identify, for example, whether you have visited
the Website before, or if you are a new visitor. Cookies may enhance your
online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a
particular site. The information collected by Google Analytics helps us analyze
how our users interact with and use the Website, compile reports on the
Website’s activity, and provide maintenance and other services related to the
Website’s activity and usage.  The
information collected and generated via Google Analytics will be transmitted to
and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s privacy policy, which can
be viewed by clicking here. To learn more about
Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of analytics tracking by
Google, click here.Sharing of User Information with Third Parties.We may share the above-identified types of user
information with third parties who perform services (such as hosting, content
management, data storage, advertising, and data analytics) on our behalf.In addition, we may share user information: (i)
with our affiliates or any successor to all or part of our business; (ii) in
order to comply with a subpoena, court order, or applicable law; and (iii) in
order to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of users, us, or the
public.Security of User Information.We take reasonable measures designed to protect user
information from unauthorized access and against unlawful processing,
accidental loss, destruction, and damage.Your Choices and Rights.Rights and Requests: You can contact us at any time using the contact
information listed in the last section of this Privacy Policy to request we do
any of the following:  (i) erase or
delete all or some of your user information; (ii) change, update, or correct
your user information; (iii) restrict how we use all or some of your user
information; (iv) access your user information and, where applicable and
feasible, request to receive that user information in a commonly used
electronic format (or ask for this information to be provided in that format to
a third party); or (v) disclose what user information we collect, use,
disclose, or sell.  We will consider and
respond to any such requests promptly, and otherwise in accordance with
applicable laws.  Although we use good
faith efforts to respond to your request, we may not be able to provide and/or
correct the requested user information in all situations.  For example, we may not be able to provide
the user information requested if it imposes an undue burden or expense,
requires us to release confidential commercial information, requires the
disclosure of user information relating to another person, or requires
authentication of the request that is not feasible.Note for California Residents: If you are a resident of California, please read
the supplemental notice to this Privacy Policy below.  The supplemental notice provides certain
information to you as required by the California Consumer Privacy Act. Note for
European Economic Area Residents: While our focus is generally on the United States, insofar as we may
from time to time process personal data of individuals in the European Union,
Iceland, Liechtenstein, Norway, or the United Kingdom, which processing may be
subject to the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”),
please note the following:The
Hinckley Company is headquartered in Portsmouth, Rhode Island, in the United
States.We will
only process your personal data to the extent applicable law allows us to do so.The United
States has not sought nor received a finding of “adequacy” from the European
Union under Article 45 of the GDPR. We rely on derogations for specific
situations as set forth in Article 49 of the GDPR. In particular, we collect
and transfer to the U.S. personal information only:  with your consent; to perform a contract with
you; or to fulfill a compelling legitimate interest in a manner that does not
outweigh your rights and freedoms.If you have
any complaints regarding our privacy practices or how we handle any requests
you make in accordance with the “Rights and Requests” section above (which
requests you may have a legal right to make and we may have a legal obligation
to honor, as dictated by applicable law), you may also lodge a complaint with
your national data protection authority.Children.Hinckley does not knowingly collect personal
information from children under the age of 13 (or 16 in Europe).  If we learn that we have collected personal
information from children under the age of 13 (or older, if applicable law
provides for different protections), then unless we obtain parental consent to
use or maintain that information, we will delete it.Contact Us.Any comments, concerns, questions, or specific
requests relating to this Privacy Policy should be directed to Hinckley at privacy@hinckleyyachts.com.If you are a resident of California, this notice
applies to you and supplements The Hinckley Company Privacy Policy. This notice
is intended to provide certain information to you as required by the California
Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”).This notice applies to information that
identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or
could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household,
such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online
identifier Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social
security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar
identifiers (“personal information”). Personal information does not include
publicly available information and certain other information that is regulated
by other applicable laws.Your rightsRight to knowYou have the right to request that we disclose
certain information to you about our collection of your personal information.
Upon our receipt of your verified request, we will provide you with:The categories of personal
information we have collected about you.The categories of sources from
which we have collected your personal information.Our business or commercial
purpose for collecting or selling your personal information. The categories of third parties
with whom we have shared your personal information. The specific pieces of personal
information we have collected about you.  We do not sell your personal
information; however, we are required to let you know that you have the
right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our
disclosures and sales of your personal information. Upon our receipt of your
verified request, we will provide you with: The categories of personal
information we have collected from you.The categories of personal
information, if any, that we have sold about you and the categories of
third parties to whom we sold such information, by category or categories
of personal information for each third party to whom the personal
information was sold.The categories of personal
information that we disclosed about you for a business purpose.  Right to opt-outWe do not sell your personal
information; however, we are required to let you know that you have the
right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information if we ever engage in
such activity. Right to deleteYou have the right at any time to request that we
delete your personal information.  Right to nondiscriminationWe will not discriminate against you for
exercising your rights under the CCPA, such as denying you products and
services, charging you different rates or prices including use of discounts or
penalties, or suggesting or providing a different level of service or quality
of products to you. However, we may charge a different price or provide a
different level or quality of products and services only if the price or
difference is directly related to the value provided to you by your personal
information.  We may offer you financial incentives, including
payments to you as compensation, for collecting, selling, or deleting your
personal information. We also may offer a different price, rate, level, or
quality of goods or services to the consumer if that price or difference is
directly related to the value provided to you by your data.ContactTo submit a request to exercise any of your
rights, please submit your request to Hinckley here.
We will evaluate the request and take action where required to do so. You may
also submit your request to privacy@hinckleyyachts.com.Depending on the nature of your request, we may
have to verify your identity when you contact us. We do this by:Requiring you to double opt-in
when submitting your consumer request by email so we can verify your email
address.Confirming your account number,
an order number and the items in such order when you identify as a
customer.   We endeavor to respond to your request as soon as
we can. If we are not able to respond to your request within 45 days, we will
let you know that we may require additional time (up to 90 total days).
You may also use an authorized agent to exercise
your rights on your behalf. If you wish to use an authorized agent, we require
that your authorized agent provides written proof to us that he or she is
authorized to act on your behalf, and we may also require your authorized agent
to verify his or her own identity.We are not able to respond to more than one “Right
to Know” request from a consumer in any 12-month period.We use cookies to offer you a better browsing experience, analyze site traffic, personalize content, and serve targeted ads. Read how we use cookies and how you can control them in our "Cookie Settings". By using our site, you consent to our use of cookies.Accept
Sign up for our Newsletter ×First Name*Last Name*E-Mail* Boating State*Outside US / CanadaAlabamaAlaskaAlbertaArizonaArkansasCalifornia - NorthCalifornia - SouthColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFlorida - East CoastFlorida - West CoastGulf CoastGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineManitobaMarylandMassachusetts - North of BostonMassachusetts - Boston and SouthMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew BrunswickNew HampshireNew Jersey - North of Sandy HookNew Jersey - South of Sandy HookNew MexicoNew York - Great LakesNew York - CoastalNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNova ScotiaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvania - EastPennsylvania - WestPuerto RicoRhode IslandSaskatchewanSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
